http://www.diabetes-book.com/privacy/

Search
Dr. Bernstein's Diabetes Solution. A Complete Guide to Achieving Normal Blood Sugars.
Overview
The owner of this website, HIPER LLC (HIPER) is committed to protecting the privacy of our users (referred to as either “you” or “Users”). HIPER uses its best efforts to ensure that the information you submit directly to HIPER remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein.
Applicability of Policy
This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected from you or submitted by you on the HIPER website, where the information is submitted directly to HIPER. The policy is not applicable to HIPER partner websites. Each participating HIPER partner website may have its own privacy policy, which we encourage you to read and understand. HIPER has no authority over any partner website’s individual privacy policy.
General Information Collected
First and foremost, HIPER does not automatically obtain any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number, or email address, when you visit our website unless you voluntarily provide such information. HIPER may, however, automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Firefox or Internet Explorer), and the Web pages you visited. This non-personally identifiable information collected by HIPER is used for the purpose of improving the HIPER website to make it more useful to you.
User Specific Information Collection
HIPER occasionally asks for personal information to fulfill your requests for contact or more information. Whenever HIPER asks for such personally identifiable information (e.g., name, address, email address, etc.), we will clearly disclose what information is required, what information is optional, and how that information may be used.
Limitations on Disclosures
Personally identifiable information in the HIPER database will not be sold or disclosed to any merchant, advertiser or Web publisher. However, HIPER does disclose aggregate information, which does not identify individuals or any personally identifiable information, to business partners, advertisers and other third parties. HIPER also reserves the right to use such non-personally identifiable information gathered on the HIPER website for promoting HIPER products and services.
Cookies
HIPER, along with thousands of other websites, uses cookies to enhance your Web-viewing experience. Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer’s hard drive to collect information about you. HIPER cookies do not damage your system or files in any way. Cookies work as follows: When you log on to the HIPER website, HIPER assigns you a unique number and records that number in the cookie file of your computer. Then, when you visit again, HIPER reads this number to help gain information about your use of our website. The HIPER cookie will not be associated with any personal information about you, and HIPER will not be able to identify you personally online. While we believe that cookies enhance your Web experience with HIPER, you have the option of setting your Web browser to reject cookies. However, doing so may negatively impact the performance of the website.
Child Privacy
HIPER does not specifically or intentionally collect information about children. If you are concerned about your child’s use of the websites, you may use Web filtering technology to supervise and limit access to websites.
Changes to Privacy Statement
This Privacy Statement may be updated from time to time. Changes to this Privacy Statement will be posted by HIPER on its website. It is your obligation to review this Privacy Statement from time to time, and your continued use of the HIPER website after changes have been posted will be deemed to be your acceptance of the revised Statement. If at any time you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement, you may contact HIPER via email at info@EHSmail.com.
Security
HIPER will maintain the confidentiality of the information that it collects during your visit to the HIPER website. HIPER maintains internal practices that help to protect the security and confidentiality of this information by limiting employee access to and use of this information.
General
This Privacy Statement is governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of New Jersey, without respect to its conflict of laws principles. Jurisdiction for any claims arising under the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement shall lie exclusively with the state and federal courts of the State of New Jersey. If any provision of this Privacy Statement is found to be invalid by a court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of this Privacy Statement, which shall remain in full force and effect.
Privacy Statement last updated, July, 2014.
ASK DR. BERNSTEIN Dr. Bernstein will participate in another 60 minute Teleseminar and Webcast on Wednesday, December 30th, 2020, at 7PM CST, 8PM EST, 6PM MST, 5PM PST designed to answer your most important questions concerning diabetes and his thoughts on the latest developments in this area. The seminar is FREE but participation will be limited and you must register.
Click here to register for the next upcoming call.
DR. BERNSTEIN'S BOOKS
Beating Diabetes eBook
1000+ Answers Your Doctor May Not Know or Tell You
...more >
Secrets to Normal Blood Sugars CD or MP3 Set
The Most Complete, Step By Step Diabetes Solution Program is now available on 5 CD’s or MP3 format
...more >
Dr. Bernstein’s Diabetes Solution
A Complete Guide to Achieving Normal Blood Sugars by Richard K. Bernstein, M.D.
...more >
The Diabetes Diet
Dr. Bernstein’s Low-Carbohydrate Solution
...more >
Dr. Richard K. Bernstein has authored six of the leading books for people managing diabetes who are interested in controlling their blood sugar to prevent the complications of diabetes. The two most recent books, “Diabetes Diet” and “The Diabetes Solution” are used by people across the world to help them in their quest to normalize their blood sugars.
ASK DR. BERNSTEIN Dr. Bernstein will participate in another 60 minute Teleseminar and Webcast on Wednesday, December 30th, 2020, at 7PM CST, 8PM EST, 6PM MST, 5PM PST designed to answer your most important questions concerning diabetes and his thoughts on the latest developments in this area. The seminar is FREE but participation will be limited and you must register.
Click here to register for the next upcoming call.
POPULAR CATEGORYArticles61Testimonials54Selected Chapters - Diabetes Solution47Videos from Diabetes University21Journal Articles20More Selections from Diabetes Solution17Advice and Commentary10
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Advertisement
Contact
© 1992-2020
Richard K. Bernstein, M.D., F.A.C.E., F.A.C.N., C.W.S., FCCWS. All Rights Reserved.
